<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-model href="CBML-schema/cbml.rng" type="application/xml" schematypens="http://relaxng.org/ns/structure/1.0"?>
<?xml-model href="CBML-schema/cbml.rng" type="application/xml" schematypens="http://purl.oclc.org/dsdl/schematron"?>
<TEI xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0" xmlns:cbml="http://www.cbml.org/ns/1.0">
    <teiHeader>
        <fileDesc>
            <titleStmt>
                <title>Amazing Spider Man</title>
                <author></author>
                <editor>Sam Sebulak</editor><!-- Which of you is editing this file? Record yourself as an editor-->
               <!-- <editor>Temitope Sakote</editor>-->
            </titleStmt>
            
            <publicationStmt>
                <publisher>...</publisher>
                <date>...</date>
                <availability status="unknown">
                    <p>...</p>
                </availability>
            </publicationStmt>
            <sourceDesc>
                <p>Printed....(explain!!!!!!!!!!!!)</p>
                <p>Retrieved rom this online resource <ptr
                    target="SET the URL FOR YOUR COMIC BOOK HERE"/></p>
            </sourceDesc>
        </fileDesc>
        <encodingDesc>
            <tagsDecl>
                <namespace name="http://www.cbml.org/ns/1.0">
                    <tagUsage gi="cbml:panel"/>
                    <tagUsage gi="cbml:caption"/>
                </namespace>
            </tagsDecl>
        </encodingDesc>
    </teiHeader>
    
    <text><body>
    <div type="page" facs="" n="2">
        <cbml:panel n="1">
            <cbml:caption> <hi rend="bold">A</hi> STORY HAS TO START <hi rend="bold">SOMEWHERE</hi>, SO LET'S BEGIN WITH A LONELY WAREHOUSE, IN THE DEAD OF NIGHT, WHERE WE FIND A ROBBERY TAKING PLACE..</cbml:caption>
            <cbml:balloon type="speech">Hold it, you guys! I think I heard somethin'!</cbml:balloon>
            <cbml:balloon type="speech">Relax, Charlie! It was probably just a mouse!</cbml:balloon>
        </cbml:panel>
        <cbml:panel n="2">
            <cbml:caption> <hi rend="bold">S</hi>UDDENLY, THE MOST AWESOME IMAGE IN CRIME-FIGHTING APPEARS ON THE WALL DIRECTLY ABOVE THE STARTLED THIEVES...</cbml:caption>
            <cbml:balloon type="speech">Mouse? You've never seen a mouse like <hi rend="bold">this</hi> before!</cbml:balloon>
            <cbml:balloon type="speech"><hi rend="bold">L-Look!</hi> It.. It's..</cbml:balloon>
        </cbml:panel>
        
    </div>
    <div type="page" facs="" n="3">
   
    <cbml:panel n="1">
        <cbml:caption> <hi rend="bold">A</hi>ND LITTLE DOES <hi rend="bold">SPIDER-MAN</hi> SUSPECT THAT HIS FRIVOLOUS WISH IS ABOUT TO COME TRUE! FOR, AT THAT MOMENT, ON THE OUTSKIRTS OF TOWN...</cbml:caption>
        <cbml:balloon type="speech">Here comes Doctor Octopus!</cbml:balloon>
        <cbml:balloon type="speech">Doctor <hi rend="bold">Octopus?</hi> Why do they call him that?</cbml:balloon>
        <cbml:balloon type="speech">Watch! You'll see in a minute!</cbml:balloon>
    </cbml:panel>
    
    <cbml:panel n="2">
        <cbml:balloon type="speech">See? It's that especially-designed contraption he wears, which enables him to perform his experiments behind the lead walls which shiled him from radiation!!</cbml:balloon>
    </cbml:panel>
    
    <cbml:panel n="3">
        <cbml:balloon type="speech">He created that get-up himself, and he's the only scientist permitted to wear it!</cbml:balloon>
        <cbml:balloon type="speech">He's the most brillian atomic-researcher in our country today!</cbml:balloon>
    </cbml:panel>
    
    <cbml:panel n="4">
        <cbml:caption> <hi rend="bold">Y</hi>ES, SUCH A MAN IS OTTO OCTAVIOUS, BETTER KNOWN TO HIS CO-WORKERS AS <hi rend="bold">DOCTOR OCTOPUS!</hi> LET US WATCH AS HE CONDUCTS A NUCLEAR EXPERIMENT...</cbml:caption>
    </cbml:panel>
    
    <cbml:panel n="3">
        <cbml:balloon type="thought">My artificial extra arms permit me to work safely with volatile chemicals which are far too dangerous to touch without protection!</cbml:balloon>
        <cbml:balloon type="thought">Though others fear radiation, I alone am able to make it my <hi rend="bold">servant!</hi></cbml:balloon>
    </cbml:panel>
    </div>
    <div type="page" facs="" n="4">
        <cbml:panel n="1">
            <cbml:caption>BUT THE WARNING, ALAS, IS GIVEN ТОО LATE! AND BEFORE THE ALARM CAN BE SOUNDED…</cbml:caption></cbml:panel>
        <cbml:panel n="2">
            <cbml:caption>THEN, AFTER THE FLAMES AND SMOKE HAVE PARTIALLY CLEARED…</cbml:caption>
            <cbml:balloon type="speech">Doctor Octopus is still breathing! I hope we've reached him in time!</cbml:balloon>
            <cbml:balloon type="speech">Even though he's still alive, he's absorbed a great deal of radiation - - poor guy!</cbml:balloon>
        </cbml:panel>

        <cbml:panel n="3">
            <cbml:caption>IN THE HOURS THAT FOLLOW, AFTER EXHAUSTIVE TESTS…</cbml:caption>
            <cbml:balloon type="speech">The x-rays show an uncertain amount of brain damage! I'm afraid his mind has been permanently damaged!</cbml:balloon>
            <cbml:balloon type="speech">We can't remove those artificial arms of his yet! The radiation has caused them to adhere to his body in some strange way!</cbml:balloon>
        </cbml:panel>
        
        <cbml:panel n="4"><cbml:caption>FINALLY, DAYS LATER, THE INJURED SCIENTIST RECOVERS CONSCIOUSNESS... </cbml:caption>
            <cbml:balloon type="speech">What am I doing here? let me get up! I must return to my work!</cbml:balloon>
            <cbml:balloon type="speech">No! you've been very ill! you must stay in bed! you need the rest!</cbml:balloon>
        </cbml:panel>
        <cbml:panel n="5"><cbml:caption>But THE BRAIN OF DR. OCTOPUS-- THE BRAIN WHICH HAS BEEN DAMAGED BY RADIATION-- REACTS IN A BITTER WAY…</cbml:caption>
            <cbml:balloon type="thought">They're jealous of me! They want to keep me from my work! But I'll show them! I'm stronger than any of them!</cbml:balloon></cbml:panel>
        <cbml:panel n="6">
            <cbml:balloon type="thought">The window is barred! They're trying to make a prisoner of me! The fools! No one can hold Doctor Octopus against his will! No one!</cbml:balloon>
        </cbml:panel> 
    </div>
        <editor>Temitope Sakote</editor>
        <div type="page" facs="" n="5">
            <cbml:panel n="1">
                <cbml:caption> <hi rend="bold">T</hi>HEN SUDDENLY, AT JUST A SUGGESTION OF A THOUGHT BY DR. OCTOPUS, HIS ARTIFICIAL ARMS MOVE AS THOUGH THEY HAVE A WILL OF THEIR OWN...</cbml:caption>
                <cbml:balloon type="thought">I’ve got to <hi rend="bold">break</hi> those bars!</cbml:balloon>
            </cbml:panel>
            <cbml:panel n="2">
                <cbml:balloon type="thought"> <hi rend="bold">I did it!!</hi> My <hi rend="bold">arms</hi> did it! Their strength is incalculable! They can do <hi rend="bold">anything!</hi> </cbml:balloon>
            </cbml:panel>
            <cbml:panel n="3">
                <cbml:balloon type="thought">Somehow, my mechanical arms have almost become a <hi rend="bold">part of me!</hi> They obey my every command with such power! And with my brilliant mind, I'm the supreme human being on Earth.</cbml:balloon>
            </cbml:panel>
            <cbml:panel n="4">
                <cbml:caption> <hi rend="bold">M</hi>INUTES LATER...</cbml:caption>
                <cbml:balloon type="speech">You wanted to see me, Dr. Octopus?</cbml:balloon>
                <cbml:balloon type="speech">Yes! Come in! Shut the door behind you!</cbml:balloon>
            </cbml:panel>
            <cbml:panel n="5">
                <cbml:balloon type="speech">What is it? You-- oh, no! <hi rend="bold">No!</hi> </cbml:balloon>
                <cbml:balloon type="speech">Ha-ha! You don't believe what you see? But it's <hi rend="bold">true!</hi> I'm <hi rend="bold">all-powerful!</hi>  From now on, <hi rend="bold">I</hi> give the commands here!</cbml:balloon>
            </cbml:panel>
            <cbml:panel n="6">
                <cbml:caption> <hi rend="bold">M</hi>EANWHILE, AT THE OFFICE OF J. JONAH JAMESON, PUBLISHER OF THE <hi rend="bold">DAILY BUGLE</hi>...</cbml:caption>
                <cbml:balloon type="speech">I WANT PICTURES OF THE INJURED HEAD SCIENTIST, DR. OCTOPUS, BUT NO ONE IS ALLOWED TO ENTER THE HOSPITAL ANYMORE!</cbml:balloon>
                <cbml:balloon type="speech">I NEVER <hi rend="bold">HEARD</hi> OF ANY HOSPITAL KEEPING PEOPLE OUT! DON'T WORRY, J.J. <hi rend="bold">I'LL</hi> GET THOSE PIX FOR YOU!</cbml:balloon>
            </cbml:panel>
            <cbml:panel n="7">
                <cbml:balloon type="speech">My best men have tried and failed! But so far you've succeeded in every assignment! I can't imagine how a teenager like you does it!</cbml:balloon>
                <cbml:balloon type="speech">Argument, J.J., is that you're never to ask me how I do it!</cbml:balloon>
            </cbml:panel>
            <cbml:panel n="8">
                <cbml:balloon type="speech">Just have a check ready for me when I bring back the pix of Dr. Octopus!</cbml:balloon>
                <cbml:balloon type="thought">He doesn't suspect Peter Parker, the teenager he assigned to the job, is going to have Spider-Man do it!</cbml:balloon>
            </cbml:panel>
        </div>
        
        <div type="page" facs="" n="6">
            <cbml:panel n="1">
                <cbml:caption> <hi rend="bold">A</hi>ND SO...</cbml:caption>
                <cbml:balloon type="thought">Here's the place! Strange that it's locked and nobody is admitted! What kind of hospital is it, anyway?</cbml:balloon>
            </cbml:panel>
            <cbml:panel n="2">
                <cbml:balloon type="thought">Well, there's <hi rend="bold">one</hi> way to find out... <hi rend="bold">Spider-Man’s</hi> just the cat to do it!</cbml:balloon>
            </cbml:panel>
            <cbml:panel n="3">
                <cbml:balloon type="thought">These suction fingers of mine will get me up the wall in <hi rend="bold">time!</hi> Boy, it's <hi rend="bold">great</hi> being <hi rend="bold">Spider-Man!</hi> I can do almost <hi rend="bold">anything!</hi> </cbml:balloon>
            </cbml:panel>
            <cbml:panel n="4">
                <cbml:balloon type="thought">The only problem is - - my jobs are <hi rend="bold">too</hi> easy! I welcome a little <hi rend="bold">competition</hi> once in a while!</cbml:balloon>
            </cbml:panel>
            <cbml:panel n="5">
                <cbml:caption> <hi rend="bold">A</hi>ND, AS HE STEADILY CLIMBS UP THE SHEER OUTER WALL, LITTLE DOES <hi rend="bold">SPIDER-MAN</hi> DREAM THAT HE IS SOON TO GET FAR <hi rend="bold">MORE</hi> "COMPETITION" THAN HE EVER BARGAINED FOR!</cbml:caption>
            </cbml:panel>
            <cbml:panel n="6">
                <cbml:caption> <hi rend="bold">S</hi>ECONDS LATER...</cbml:caption>
                <cbml:balloon type="thought">Almost there!</cbml:balloon>
            </cbml:panel>
            <cbml:panel n="7">
                <cbml:balloon type="thought"> <hi rend="bold">Holy mackerel!</hi> What's <hi rend="bold">that?</hi> </cbml:balloon>
                <cbml:balloon type="speech"> <hi rend="bold">Silence!</hi> Nobody is to speak when <hi rend="bold">Dr. Octopus</hi> speaks!</cbml:balloon>
            </cbml:panel>
        </div>
        
        <div type="page" facs="" n="7">
            <cbml:panel n="1">
                <cbml:caption> <hi rend="bold">P</hi>EERING UNSEEN THROUGH THE LARGE PICTURE WINDOW, <hi rend="bold">SPIDER-MAN</hi> WITNESSES A STRANGE, UNEXPECTED SIGHT...</cbml:caption>
                <cbml:balloon type="speech">You can’t keep all of us prisoners <hi rend="bold">forever</hi> , Doctor Octopus! We've done what you asked—gotten you all the equipment you wanted! When will you let us go?</cbml:balloon>
                <cbml:balloon type="speech">Not until <hi rend="bold">I'm</hi> ready! With my powers, <hi rend="bold">no one</hi> can resist me! You'll remain to serve me until I no longer need you—and not before!</cbml:balloon>
                <cbml:balloon type="thought">Well, well! So the good doc has flipped his lid, eh? Well, this is just what I’ve been <hi rend="bold">hopin'</hi> for—a little <hi rend="bold">action!</hi> </cbml:balloon>
            </cbml:panel>
            <cbml:panel n="2">
                <cbml:balloon type="speech">But this is <hi rend="bold">mad!</hi> You have no right—</cbml:balloon>
                <cbml:balloon type="speech"> <hi rend="bold">Right?!</hi> You dare speak to me of right?</cbml:balloon>
            </cbml:panel>
            <cbml:panel n="3">
                <cbml:balloon type="speech">I have the <hi rend="bold">right</hi>to do <hi rend="bold">anything—</hi>as long as I have the <hi rend="bold">power!</hi> And if you <hi rend="bold">doubt</hi> my power, here is a small sample...</cbml:balloon>
                <cbml:balloon type="speech">No! <hi rend="bold">Don’t!</hi> Let me down!</cbml:balloon>
            </cbml:panel>
            <cbml:panel n="4">
                <cbml:balloon type="thought">Looks like it’s time for <hi rend="bold">Spider-Man</hi> to join the party before he really hurts that fella!</cbml:balloon>
            </cbml:panel>
            <cbml:panel n="5">
                <cbml:balloon type="speech">Hold it, doc! How about picking on someone who can fight you back?</cbml:balloon>
                <cbml:balloon type="speech"> <hi rend="bold">Spider-Man!</hi> </cbml:balloon>
            </cbml:panel>
            <cbml:panel n="6">
                <cbml:balloon type="speech">Well, I sure ain’t Albert Schweitzer!</cbml:balloon>
                <cbml:balloon type="speech">You dare speak flippantly to <hi rend="bold">me!</hi> You fool! When I'm finished with you, you’ll sing a <hi rend="bold">different</hi> tune!</cbml:balloon>
            </cbml:panel>
        </div>
        <div type="page" facs="" n="8">
            <cbml:panel n="1">
                <cbml:balloon type="speech">You don’t think those dumb-looking flappers of yours can move fast enough to catch <hi rend="bold">Spider-Man</hi>, do you?</cbml:balloon>
            </cbml:panel>
            <cbml:panel n="2">
                <cbml:balloon type="speech"><hi rend="bold">HEY...!! WHA—?</hi></cbml:balloon>
            </cbml:panel>
        </div>
    </body>
 </text>
</TEI>
