<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-model href="CBML-schema/cbml.rng" type="application/xml" schematypens="http://relaxng.org/ns/structure/1.0"?>
<?xml-model href="CBML-schema/cbml.rng" type="application/xml" schematypens="http://purl.oclc.org/dsdl/schematron"?>
<TEI xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0" xmlns:cbml="http://www.cbml.org/ns/1.0">
    <teiHeader>
        <fileDesc>
            <titleStmt>
                <title>Amazing Spider Man</title>
                <author></author>
                <editor>Sam Sebulak</editor><!-- Which of you is editing this file? Record yourself as an editor-->
               <!-- <editor>Temitope Sakote</editor>-->
            </titleStmt>
            
            <publicationStmt>
                <publisher>...</publisher>
                <date>...</date>
                <availability status="unknown">
                    <p>...</p>
                </availability>
            </publicationStmt>
            <sourceDesc>
                <p>Printed....(explain!!!!!!!!!!!!)</p>
                <p>Retrieved rom this online resource <ptr
                    target="SET the URL FOR YOUR COMIC BOOK HERE"/></p>
            </sourceDesc>
        </fileDesc>
        <encodingDesc>
            <tagsDecl>
                <namespace name="http://www.cbml.org/ns/1.0">
                    <tagUsage gi="cbml:panel"/>
                    <tagUsage gi="cbml:caption"/>
                </namespace>
            </tagsDecl>
        </encodingDesc>
    </teiHeader>
    
    <text><body>
    <div type="page" facs="" n="2">
        <cbml:panel n="1">
            <cbml:caption> <hi rend="bold">A</hi> STORY HAS TO START <hi rend="bold">SOMEWHERE</hi>, SO LET'S BEGIN WITH A LONELY WAREHOUSE, IN THE DEAD OF NIGHT, WHERE WE FIND A ROBBERY TAKING PLACE..</cbml:caption>
            <cbml:balloon type="speech">Hold it, you guys! I think I heard somethin'!</cbml:balloon>
            <cbml:balloon type="speech">Relax, Charlie! It was probably just a mouse!</cbml:balloon>
        </cbml:panel>
        <cbml:panel n="2">
            <cbml:caption> <hi rend="bold">S</hi>UDDENLY, THE MOST AWESOME IMAGE IN CRIME-FIGHTING APPEARS ON THE WALL DIRECTLY ABOVE THE STARTLED THIEVES...</cbml:caption>
            <cbml:balloon type="speech">Mouse? You've never seen a mouse like <hi rend="bold">this</hi> before!</cbml:balloon>
            <cbml:balloon type="speech"><hi rend="bold">L-Look!</hi> It.. It's..</cbml:balloon>
        </cbml:panel>
        
    </div>
    <div type="page" facs="" n="3">
   
    <cbml:panel n="1">
        <cbml:caption> <hi rend="bold">A</hi>ND LITTLE DOES <hi rend="bold">SPIDER-MAN</hi> SUSPECT THAT HIS FRIVOLOUS WISH IS ABOUT TO COME TRUE! FOR, AT THAT MOMENT, ON THE OUTSKIRTS OF TOWN...</cbml:caption>
        <cbml:balloon type="speech">Here comes Doctor Octopus!</cbml:balloon>
        <cbml:balloon type="speech">Doctor <hi rend="bold">Octopus?</hi> Why do they call him that?</cbml:balloon>
        <cbml:balloon type="speech">Watch! You'll see in a minute!</cbml:balloon>
    </cbml:panel>
    
    <cbml:panel n="2">
        <cbml:balloon type="speech">See? It's that especially-designed contraption he wears, which enables him to perform his experiments behind the lead walls which shiled him from radiation!!</cbml:balloon>
    </cbml:panel>
    
    <cbml:panel n="3">
        <cbml:balloon type="speech">He created that get-up himself, and he's the only scientist permitted to wear it!</cbml:balloon>
        <cbml:balloon type="speech">He's the most brillian atomic-researcher in our country today!</cbml:balloon>
    </cbml:panel>
    
    <cbml:panel n="4">
        <cbml:caption> <hi rend="bold">Y</hi>ES, SUCH A MAN IS OTTO OCTAVIOUS, BETTER KNOWN TO HIS CO-WORKERS AS <hi rend="bold">DOCTOR OCTOPUS!</hi> LET US WATCH AS HE CONDUCTS A NUCLEAR EXPERIMENT...</cbml:caption>
    </cbml:panel>
    
    <cbml:panel n="3">
        <cbml:balloon type="thought">My artificial extra arms permit me to work safely with volatile chemicals which are far too dangerous to touch without protection!</cbml:balloon>
        <cbml:balloon type="thought">Though others fear radiation, I alone am able to make it my <hi rend="bold">servant!</hi></cbml:balloon>
    </cbml:panel>
    </div>
    <div type="page" facs="" n="4">
        <cbml:panel n="1">
            <cbml:caption>BUT THE WARNING, ALAS, IS GIVEN ТОО LATE! AND BEFORE THE ALARM CAN BE SOUNDED…</cbml:caption></cbml:panel>
        <cbml:panel n="2">
            <cbml:caption>THEN, AFTER THE FLAMES AND SMOKE HAVE PARTIALLY CLEARED…</cbml:caption>
            <cbml:balloon type="speech">Doctor Octopus is still breathing! I hope we've reached him in time!</cbml:balloon>
            <cbml:balloon type="speech">Even though he's still alive, he's absorbed a great deal of radiation - - poor guy!</cbml:balloon>
        </cbml:panel>

        <cbml:panel n="3">
            <cbml:caption>IN THE HOURS THAT FOLLOW, AFTER EXHAUSTIVE TESTS…</cbml:caption>
            <cbml:balloon type="speech">The x-rays show an uncertain amount of brain damage! I'm afraid his mind has been permanently damaged!</cbml:balloon>
            <cbml:balloon type="speech">We can't remove those artificial arms of his yet! The radiation has caused them to adhere to his body in some strange way!</cbml:balloon>
        </cbml:panel>
        
        <cbml:panel n="4"><cbml:caption>FINALLY, DAYS LATER, THE INJURED SCIENTIST RECOVERS CONSCIOUSNESS... </cbml:caption>
            <cbml:balloon type="speech">What am I doing here? let me get up! I must return to my work!</cbml:balloon>
            <cbml:balloon type="speech">No! you've been very ill! you must stay in bed! you need the rest!</cbml:balloon>
        </cbml:panel>
        <cbml:panel n="5"><cbml:caption>But THE BRAIN OF DR. OCTOPUS-- THE BRAIN WHICH HAS BEEN DAMAGED BY RADIATION-- REACTS IN A BITTER WAY…</cbml:caption>
            <cbml:balloon type="thought">They're jealous of me! They want to keep me from my work! But I'll show them! I'm stronger than any of them!</cbml:balloon></cbml:panel>
        <cbml:panel n="6">
            <cbml:balloon type="thought">The window is barred! They're trying to make a prisoner of me! The fools! No one can hold Doctor Octopus against his will! No one!</cbml:balloon>
        </cbml:panel> 
    </div></body></text>
</TEI>
